字幕校订：gemini0421  来源：破烂熊
美国空军和海军
Air and naval forces of the United States
对恐怖组织设施进行了一系列的打击行动
launched a series of strikes against terrorist facilities...
泛美航空103号航班坠毁于洛克比镇
Pan Am flight 103 crashed into the town of Lockerbie.
他在非洲 欧洲和中东都制裁过恐怖行动
He has sanctioned acts of terror in Africa, Europe and the Middle East.
针对科威特的侵略是不会长久的
This will not stand, this aggression against, uh, Kuwait.
这种对恐怖主义赤裸裸的追求
This relentless pursuit of terror.
我们会一视同仁
We will make no distinction...
科尔号驱逐舰在亚丁港加油时遭到袭击
The USS Cole was attacked while refueling in the port of Aden.
这是一次恐怖袭击
This was an act of terrorism.
是卑鄙而软弱的行径
It was a despicable and cowardly act.
我们为您带来的下一首桑巴是一首怀旧金曲
The next samba we're going to swing for you is one of the good old favorites.
直到他被阻止
...until something stops him.
就在我的眼前 我完全没有料到会处这种事
It was right in front of my eyes, and I never saw it coming.
那飞机直冲着世贸大楼撞了过去
That plane crashed into the World Trade Center.
上千的民众在逃命
Thousands of people running.
我们必须也会在国内外保持警惕
We must and we will remain vigilant at home and abroad.
你是我认识的最聪明 也是最笨的人
You're the smartest and the dumbest fucking person I've ever known.
弄错的人可不是我
I'm not the one who got it wrong.
只有我做对了
I'm the only one who got it right.
拿下他们
Take 'em.
统统拿下
Take 'em all.
前情提要
Previously on Homeland...
我昨天和总统谈过了
I spoke to the President yesterday.
他想要对情报工作做出一些调整
He's exploring some changes in intelligence practice.
我不会为了让你支持我当局长
而改变自己的看法
I won't temper my views just to get your support for my confirmation as Director.
被提名为局长的是我
I'm the one getting nominated as Director.
现在这个局子一团乱
The Agency is being driven into the fucking ground.
我们希望你能成为你在参议院以及
专责委员会上所承诺的改革者
The hope is that you are the reformer your record in the Senate would indicate.
那就是说你决定接受改革了?
So, then, you agree that change is in order?
- 是的
- 那是Javadi吗?
Yes, I do. Is that Javadi?
和我们的妻子在德黑兰的一家法式餐厅里
In a French restaurant in Tehran with their wives.
我们当时是国王执政末期的年轻情报官
We were young intelligence officers during the dying days of the Shah.
我眼看着一个我自以为了解的人变成野兽
I watched the man I thought I knew become an animal.
所以这次行动是你的报复?
So this operation is your revenge?
我的报复是在四个月后帮助他的妻儿逃到美国
Revenge was when I helped his wife and son escape to the West four months later.
我需要你去盯着Carrie
我们放她出去引伊朗人上钩
I need your eyes on Carrie. We dangled her to draw the Iranians out.
- 正是Javadi本人
- Carrie Mathison
Javadi himself. Carrie Mathison.
- 我们现在是不是独处?
- 没有人在监听
Are we completely alone now? No one is listening.
我们来谈谈Nasser Hejazi吧
It's time we talk about Nasser Hejazi.
你用他的名字从革命卫队那里
侵吞了超过四千五百万美元
Whose name you used to embezzle more than $45 million dollars.
- 你现在是你自己国家的敌人
- 那为什么我还没有被捕?
You are now an enemy of your own state. So why am I not arrested already?
- Saul想先和你谈谈
- 他会屈服的 对不对?
Saul would like to talk to you first. He will turn, won't he?
让一个情报官员背叛自己的国家
Turning an intelligence officer against his own country.
没有什么工作比这个更微妙且无法捉摸
Well, that's the most delicate and uncertain work there is.
他不肯立刻跟我来 说不想惊动他的人
He wouldn't come with me right away. Said it wouldn't fly with his guys.
太冒险了 所以我和他定了见面时间
It was too risky. So I set a meet for later.
原计划是直接带他来这里
Plan was to bring him straight here.
需要帮助吗?
Can I help you?
- 住手 不然我开枪了
- 现在我准备好去见Saul了
Stop or I shoot. Now I'm ready to see Saul.
死了两个人 有很多血
这里他妈都血流成河了 Saul
There's two fatalities and a lot of blood. It's a fucking bloodbath, Saul.
尽快把他带离那里 带上凶器
You got to get him out of there as fast as possible. And get the murder weapon.
孩子要怎么办?
What do we do about the baby?
别管他 你们不能留下踪迹
Leave it. You weren't there.
你看起来不像是一个刚刚得到
自己职业生涯中最大资产的人
You don't look like a man who just landed the biggest asset of his career.
-==破烂熊乐园倾情奉献==-
本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业用途
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
国土 第三季第7集
-=破烂熊字幕组=-
翻译：菱子 Louvre
校对：酒囊饭袋
时间轴：RoyJames
-=破烂熊字幕组=-
- 我们要找什么?
- 一把.22口径手枪
So, what are we looking for here? A.22...
还有这只瓶子的上半段
and the top half of this bottle.
梅子酒
Plum wine.
是啊 伊朗产的一种酒
Yeah, some kind of Iranian thing.
我还以为穆斯林不喝酒呢
I thought Muslims didn't drink.
- 多少下?
- 什么?
How many? What?
他扎了她多少下?
He hit her how many times?
粗略看来至少有十几下
I can see at least a dozen separate strikes.
说实话 用这东西的话...谁数得清啊?
Honestly, though, with this... who the hell knows?
- Cal?
- 我们还在找凶器呢 Cort
Cal? We're still looking for the murder weapons here, Cort.
我有更好的消息 邻居的监控摄像头拍到了这个
I may have something better. Neighbor's security camera picked it up.
每月的第一个周五 德黑兰的阿斯卡利银行
Money is wired from the Al Askari Bank in Tehran
就会把钱汇到卡拉卡斯西班牙拉丁商会的分会
the first Friday of every month to the HLBC subsidiary in Caracas.
这里有你的签名
On your signature there.
我们顺着钱查下去 查到了一系列的恐怖行动
We have traced the funds downstream to a series of terrorist actions,
包括对CIA的攻击
including the attack on the CIA.
但是钱也进了你自己的私人账户
你侵吞了革命卫队差不多五千万美元
But also to your personal accounts where you've diverted nearly $50 million of Revolutionary Guard money.
如果伊斯兰革命卫队发现的话 你死罪难逃
That's punishable by death if the IRGC were to find out.
你想说什么 Saul?
What's your point, Saul?
被个丫头拉下了马?
That I've been brought down by a girl?
被两个丫头?
By two girls?
够了
Enough.
我想他了解自己的处境
I think he appreciates the situation.
- 他很会操纵人 他很擅长
- 我知道
He manipulates people. That's what he does. I know.
别让他得逞了
You can't let him get to you.
他得逞了
Well, he does.
你是在哪儿找到她的?
Where'd you find that one?
满腔怒火的伊朗难民多着呢
The list of outraged Iranian exiles is long.
她不会干很久的
She won't last.
啊 1976年你就这么说过我
Well, that's what you said about me in 1976.
那时我们才刚开始
When we were both starting out.
所以你抓到我了
So you got me.
你觉得自豪吗?
Are you proud of yourself?
目前是
So far.
我知道你要什么
I know what you want.
是什么?
What's that?
让我把知道的都说出来
To clean me of what I know.
我猜你一定很想知道我国核武器计划的进展 啊?
I imagine the state of our nuclear weapons program is high on your list, huh?
你要和我做交易
There is a deal to be made.
不然我早进监狱了
Or I'd be in prison by now.
如果我开口...
If I talk...
如果我那么做的话
if I do that,
我需要保护
I need protection.
给我在迈阿密找一个安全的房子 要带警卫
I need a secure compound in Miami with a guard detail.
然后把我的钱解冻
And I want my money unfrozen.
所有的钱
All of it.
就这些?
Is that everything?
目前就这些
For now.
所以你已经想过了?
So you've put some thought into this?
这就是我的条件
Those are my terms.
好
Okay.
那是你的条件
Those are your terms.
但是问题是你弄错了
But the problem is you got it all wrong.
因为我想从你那儿得到的不只是情报
'Cause what I want from you is not just intelligence.
你觉得我为什么要历尽千辛万苦
找出你的金融劣迹?
Why do you think I went through the trouble of documenting your financial misdeeds?
为什么?
Why?
你杀了219个美国人
You killed 219 Americans.
你以为我在乎你侵吞革命卫队的钱啊?
Think I care you also ripped off the Revolutionary Guard?
我早给你定好了计划
I got plans for you.
你透露一两个国家机密就想脱身是不可能的
Much bigger than you spilling a few state secrets.
什么计划?
What plans?
我要把你派回伊朗
I'm gonna play you back into Iran.
从现在起 你为我们工作
From now on, you work for us.
为我
For me.
我是你的新情报官员
I'm your new case officer.
行不通的
It won't work.
- 为什么?
- 你让我暴露了
Why's that? You burned me back home.
- 怎么说?
- 我和你见过面了
- How? - I'm here with you.
- 他们可不知道
- 他们会知道的
- They don't know that. - Oh, they will.
谁会告诉他们啊? 我不会 你不会
Who's going to tell them? Not me, not you.
你自愿来到这里
You came here under your own steam.
不管你是怎么进来的 你的故事还是说得通的
However you managed that, your story's still intact.
如果我拒绝离开呢?
And if I refuse to go?
明白了吗?
So we're clear?
要么我送你回伊朗 要么就是另一条路
I'm sending you back to Tehran one way or the other.
不当我的情报员就当革命的叛军吧
Either as my asset or a traitor to the Revolution.
- 他一开始的计划就是这个?
- 嘘
- Was this always the plan? - Shh.
别以为我不会 Majid
Don't think I won't, Majid.
那里可没有法庭 也不会让你一死了之
That's not a trial and quick execution you're facing there.
首先你会受到折磨
You'll be tortured first.
我也知道当众吊死现在又重新流行起来了
And I understand public hangings are back in vogue.
你想知道什么 我都说
I will tell you everything you want to know,
我毫无保留地告诉你 但是我不能回去
chapter and verse, but I can't go back.
- 你两件事都得做
- 不 我不做
You will do both. No, I won't.
- 你必须得这么做
- 我不做!
- Yes, you will. - No, I won't!
你流血了
You're bleeding.
下午好
Good afternoon.
- 嗯
- 晚上过得很糟?
Yeah. Rough night?
- 也没有
- 你看起来很累
Not especially. You look tired.
想喝点什么吗?
Can I get you anything?
你已经失踪很久了
You've been MIA for days now.
不算是失踪吧
Not really.
我在这里啊
I've been here.
你旷工了 Saul也是
You've been absent. Saul, too.
能不能解释一下?
You care to shed any light on that?
去和Saul谈吧
Talk to Saul.
我说过了 很难找到他的人
Like I said, he's not so easy to find.
你是我的人 Peter
You're my guy, Peter.
是我把你招进来 训练你的
I recruited you. I brought you up.
- 你想说什么?
- 我想说的是我希望从你嘴里
- What's your point? - My point is that entitles me to a certain amount of forthrightness.
听到实话
From you.
Bethesda今早出了一起双重谋杀案
There was a double murder earlier today in Bethesda.
Fariba Javadi 伊朗安全局副局长的前妻
Fariba Javadi, ex-wife of the Iranian Deputy Security Chief.
还有她的儿媳
Also her daughter-in-law.
我知道这是一起该死的屠杀
I understand it was a damn slaughter.
你想要我帮你查查么?
Would you like me to look into it for you?
滚你妈的
Fuck you.
这是在案发现场门外拍到的
That's outside the house where it happened.
下午2点53分 你是主要嫌疑人
2:53 PM. You're the main suspect.
我真他妈希望他们把你钉死在墙上
I hope they nail your ass to the wall.
- Saul在哪里?
- 在审讯室里
- Where's Saul? - In the interrogation room.
你知道我们要把Javadi送回伊朗吗?
Did you know we're sending Javadi back to Iran?
你错过好戏了
You missed the fireworks.
Javadi听到自己要回去以后魂都吓没了
我们得等到他把血止住
Javadi blew when he found out he had to go back. We're on hold till they stop the bleeding.
- 最好不要等太久
- 该死
We better not wait too long. Shit.
我刚要重新开始 怎么了?
I'm about to start again. What's the deal?
小区里的监控录像拍到我了
警方放出了全境通缉
Neighbor's security camera picked me up. There's an APB out.
- 只是你?
- 是的 不知道为什么没拍到Javadi和Carrie
Just you? Yeah, somehow it missed Javadi and Carrie.
- 从哪儿弄到的?
- Dar Adal 记录是他监视着的
Where'd you get this? Dar Adal. He monitors the blotters.
- 所以他知道Javadi入境了?
- 他知道出事了 但是不知道实情
So he knows Javadi's in the country? He knows something's up; he's not in on it.
我建议你赶快去找他谈谈
I suggest you go talk to him soon.
- 我会的
- 我是说马上
- I will. - I mean now.
- 他很火大
- 我会把事情压下去 与此同时
He's furious. I'll smooth things over. In the meantime,
你躲在这里不要出去 我们不能让你被捕
you need to stay out of sight here in this building. We can't risk having you arrested.
- 好吧 但是我们要怎么做?
- Bethesda警局有个队长欠我一个人情
Fine, but what do we do about this? There's a police captain in Bethesda who owes me.
我可以打电话给他 至少让他撤下照片
I could call him, at least get the photo down off the wire.
去吧 去和他面谈 用你国家安全局的身份
Do it, face-to-face. Play the national security card.
告诉他我在背后全力支持你
Tell him you have my full support.
万一他要谋杀的细节怎么办?
What if he wants details about the murder?
不能告诉他
He can't have them.
如果任何人猜到Javadi在境内 我们就完了
If anyone even suspects Javadi's in the country, we're through.
去啊
Well?
我查了整幢房子的监控 我一定是忘了邻居家的
I checked the whole house for surveillance. I must have missed the neighbors.
- 是啊 我他妈整件事情都搞砸了
- 进行得怎样了?
Yeah, well, I missed the whole fucking thing. How's it going in there?
很慢
Slowly.
- 有困难?
- 哦 我们会有办法的
Trouble? Oh, we'll manage.
你看起来很不高兴
You seem upset.
这样就好了
That's good enough.
- 嗯?
- 嗯什么?
Well? Well what?
你有没有接受目前的状况?
Have you come to terms with your situation?
怎么进行?
How does it work?
我们尽快把你送回你的国家
We return you to your people as soon as possible.
我假设他们已经给你找好了离开本国的路径
I assume they've arranged a way for you to get out of the country.
不 我是说Fariba
No, I meant about Fariba.
这宗罪行必须得掩饰过去
A crime is committed that must be covered up.
这里的程序是什么?
How does it work here?
你杀了她
You killed her.
为什么?
Why?
尽你所能来回击我?
Get back at me because you could?
她是我的妻子 她对我不忠
She was my wife. She was unfaithful.
她是你的前妻 都是35年前的事了
She was your ex-wife. It was 35 years ago.
在神看来 我们还是夫妻
In the eyes of God, we're still married.
我应该用石头砸死她
I should have stoned her to death,
但是你给我的时间不够
but you didn't give me enough time.
还记得这个吗?
Remember this?
是Fariba的21岁生日
It was Fariba's 21st birthday.
我们谈了一整晚 我们四个人
We talked all night, the four of us,
谈论未来会带给我们什么
about what the future might bring.
不该是这样的
It wasn't this.
Carrie?
- 不是说到外面去谈么
- 我的人有几个问题
I thought we were meeting outside. My guys have a few questions.
你告诉他们我不能说 对吧?
You told them I can't talk about it, right?
是的 我和他们说了
Yeah, I told them.
Johnson警探
Detectives Johnson,
Cort警探 Carrie Mathison
Cort, Carrie Mathison.
好吧 我知道这样你们不高兴
Okay, I understand you're not happy about this.
- 哦 你高兴么?
- 当然不高兴了
Oh, and you are? Of course not.
我们和你们一样不满
We're as upset as you.
- 这人是谁啊?
- 我恐怕不能说
So who's this guy? I'm afraid that's classified.
- 但是他是你们的人?
- 嗯 这点也不能说
But he's one of yours? Well, that's classified, too.
- 你能告诉我他在这里干什么吗?
- 我不能...
Can you tell me what he was doing here? That's...
你能告诉我他怎么认识受害人的吗?
Can you tell me how he knew the victims?
- 好吧 等下
- 你他妈能告诉我什么啊?
- Okay, wait a second. - Can you tell me any goddamn thing at all?
你能告诉我为什么这位女士会躺在这里
喉咙被人割烂了?
Can you tell me why this lady's laying here with her throat cut to ribbons?
你到底能他妈说什么?
Any fucking thing?
失陪
Excuse me.
好吧 队长?
Okay, Cap?
你不是个狂热分子 你很现实
You're not a fanatic. You're a pragmatist.
一直都是
Always have been.
我是谁不是谁轮不到你来说
Don't tell me what I am and what I am not.
我们都老了 这点没什么可争的吧
Well, we're both old men. There's no disputing that.
的确
We are.
年纪大的诅咒就是你会意识到
最终我们什么也控制不了
It's the curse of old men to realize that in the end, we control nothing.
所以我们要爆发
So we lash out.
布宜诺斯艾利斯 柏林
Buenos Aires, Berlin...
卑尔根(挪威城市)
Bergen.
这些都是小打小闹 Majid
These are small acts, Majid.
跟你配不上
Unworthy of you.
你漏了一点
You left something out.
CIA爆炸案
The bombing of the CIA.
这可不小
Nothing small about that.
- 这可就配得上了
- 我本来也想和你谈谈那事的
Nothing unworthy. Well, I wanted to talk about that, too.
- 你当然想了
- 因为当爆炸发生以后
I'm sure you do. Because when that bomb went off,
死了那么多的人
killing all those people,
很多是我的朋友
many of them my friends,
我的第一个念头
my first thought
不是复仇
was not revenge.
而是...
It was...
"我们得做出改变"
"Something has to change. "
以牙还牙 以眼还眼
You hit us, we hit you.
总是一成不变
It's always the same.
那么...
And...
我作为你的间谍回国会改变这一切吗?
how does my going back as your spy change any of that?
常年以来 我们在后台辛勤劳作 你和我
For years, we toiled in back rooms, you and I.
我们辛勤劳作
We toiled
让肤浅之辈在舞台上亮相
while shallower men held the stage,
等待我们上台的那一刻
waiting for our time to come,
渐渐意识到那一刻永远不会来
gradually understanding it never would.
突然 这一刻来了
Now it has, unexpectedly.
对你来说 是来了
For you, it has.
你是那个让一切变成可能的人
You're the one who made it possible.
我想要还情
I want to return the favor.
你觉得这像是在还情吗 Saul?
Does this look like a favor to you, Saul?
Majid 多亏了你 我得以站在舞台的正中央
Majid, thanks to you, I stand at the center of things.
我的权力是你赐予的
You put me in power.
你回德黑兰去 我也会为你做同样的事
You go back to Tehran, I'll do the same for you.
我知道一个方法
I know a way.
你没事吧?
You all right?
是的 抱歉 我不知道发生了什么事
Yeah, sorry. I don't know what happened there.
- 所以我们说定了?
- 我可不觉得 不行
So are we okay? I wouldn't say so, no.
抱歉 你不能把这事处理掉吗?
I'm sorry, but can't you handle that?
你是说 我不能以长官身份把这事压下去吗?
You mean, can't I just pull rank and shut this thing down?
当然了 你现在不也正在压我呢吗
但是你知道接下来会怎样吗?
Sure, just like you try with me. But you know what happens next?
那张照片和这房间里的所有证据都会
Somehow that photo and all the evidence in this room
莫名其妙出现在德拉吉报道
甚至该死的维基泄密上面
show up on Drudge Report or goddamn Wikileaks,
到那时你才真是遇上麻烦了
and then you've got yourself a real problem.
别用那种我一点忙也帮不上的眼神看我
And don't look at me like I'm being less than helpful.
我只是告诉你事实而已
I'm just talking reality here.
那你说怎么办?
So what do you suggest?
他们想要和照片里的人谈谈
They want to talk to the guy in the photo.
- 那不可能
- 你想不想悄无声息地解决这事啊?
- That's impossible. - You want this thing closed quietly?
那就想个办法
Find a way.
- Quinn哪儿去了?
- 呃 外面吧 大概
Where's Quinn? Uh, outside, I think.
- 能找到他吗?
- 是不是计划从一开始就是把他送回伊朗?
Could you find him? Was it always the plan to send Javadi back to Iran?
- 希望是如此
- 没人告诉我
It was always the hope. No one told me.
嗯 自豪点吧 这都是你达成的
Well, you should be proud. Your work made it all possible.
我才不自豪 他对这个国家做的事情
比起他对伊朗做的事来简直是九牛一毛
I'm not proud. What he did to this country, it's nothing compared to what he did to Iran.
- 我们应该让他上法庭
- 计划不是那样的
- We should try him for what he's done. - That's not the plan.
计划不是这样的 请帮我找到Quinn
That's not the plan. Go find Quinn, please.
- 他同意了
- 很好
- He's in. - Good.
- 你那边处理得怎样了?
- 不太好
How'd you make out? Not so well.
当地警察想找你谈谈
They want to talk to you- the local cops do.
- 你告诉他们不可能 对吧?
- 说过好几遍
- You told them that was impossible, right? - Several times.
我还以为你的队长朋友会把这事处理掉
I thought your captain friend was gonna take care of this.
是啊 我本来也希望的 被他耍了
Yeah, me, too. He boned me.
最重要的是不能危害到Javadi计划
The important thing here is to not jeopardize the Javadi play.
对吧? 那我去和当地警察谈谈
Agreed? So let me talk to them, the cops.
- 你要怎么说?
- 我不知道 看他们问什么吧
And say what? I don't know, see what they ask.
你知道他们会怎么问
You know what they'll ask.
你是他们唯一的嫌疑人
既然你不能告诉他们事实是什么
You're their only suspect,
and since you can't tell them what actually happened,
你就得承认自己杀了两个人
还不准他们逮捕你
you'll be admitting to two murders
and then saying they can't touch you for it.
好吧
Okay.
听着 警方可能会危及到我们的行动
Look, we have police threatening to blow up our operation.
我们至少也得要争取时间把Javadi弄出国去
At the very least, this buys us enough time to get Javadi out of the country.
除非你还有其他选择 先这么做吧
So unless you got another option? Do it.
- 至少让我和他一起去
- 不 Javadi来这里是和你联系
At least let me go with him. No. Javadi came here to contact you.
只有你才能和他在公众场合出现
我需要你送他回他自己人那里去
You're the only one who can be seen with him. I need you to get him back to his people.
- 什么时候?
- 越快越好
- When? - Soon as possible.
你得在发生其他爆炸案之前把他弄出国去
You got to get him out of the country before anything else blows up,
我要你一直呆在他身边
我们不能再搞砸了 懂吗?
and you need to stay right by his side. We cannot risk another screwup, okay?
- 你要去哪里?
- 我要去见Lockhart议员 他已经注意到
- Where will you be? - I got a meeting with Senator Lockhart, who's apparently noticed
我这周都没在办公室露过脸了
I haven't been at my office all week.
我们得把这事保密到Javadi坐上
回伊朗的飞机去为止
We need to keep this thing together until Javadi's on a plane heading back to Iran.
时间到了 Carrie会送你回去
It's time. Carrie will take you back.
你怎么知道我不会就此消失?
And what makes you sure I won't just vanish?
这边
This way.
她会一直把你送上飞机
She'll be with you all the way to the plane.
我是说在伊朗
I meant in Iran.
我以前说过 这一切都是你开头的
What I said before. You started this.
我觉得你会很想看结局如何的
I think you'll want to be there when it ends.
在你走之前我得弄清楚一件事
I need to know something before you leave.
我需要知道
I need to know.
是谁放的炸弹
Who was responsible for the bomb?
- 兰利的那个?
- 是
The bomb at Langley? Yes.
那天在地上的炸弹 是谁放的
On the ground that day. Who was responsible?
我觉得是Brody 你是这么告诉参议院的
I thought it was Brody. That's what you told the Senate.
也是这么告诉全世界的
That's what you told the entire world.
全世界都在追捕他 还有一千万的悬赏金
You have a manhunt on five continents, a $10 million reward...
是他做的吗 是或不是
Did he do it? Yes or no.
- 我不知道
- 我不相信你
I don't know. I don't believe you.
- 我不...
- 看着我的眼睛 回答我
- I don't... - Look me in the eye and answer.
不是他
It wasn't him.
是Abu Nazir的人干的
It was one of Abu Nazir's guys.
具体是谁放的
Who, exactly...
我当时并不想知道
I didn't want to know.
我们会给你一些衣服让你换上
We'll get you some clothes to change into.
然后Carrie会带你回到你的飞机上
Then Carrie will take you back to your plane.
- 可以等一下我吗
- 好的 先生
Will you give me a sec? Yes, sir.
Saul? 你在哪儿
Saul? Where are you?
- 我在开车
- 回家吗
Driving. Home?
不 回去工作
No. Back to work.
我一直在想我们在德黑兰的那段日子
I've been thinking about our days in Tehran.
是吗
Really?
那是很久以前了
That was... a long time ago.
是啊 我们当时那么年轻
Yep. We were so young.
当一切都毁了以后我是那么的担心你
I was so worried about you when it all went to hell.
想着怎么救你出来
About getting you out.
不 我也很担心你
Yeah, no, I was... worried about you.
因为我抛下你自己跑了
Leaving you behind.
我说过我不在意你在孟买的那些朋友
其实我在意
I said I didn't care about your friend from Mumbai, but I do.
我当时还说自己并没有你的所有权
I said I didn't have any claim on you.
- Saul
- 但是我有
Saul... But I do.
也许这些只是我的一己之见吧
Maybe it's just in my own mind at this point.
我也不知道 但我必须在一切都太迟了之前告诉你
I don't know. But I needed to tell you before it's too late.
- 你在听吗
- 在
Did you hear me? Yes.
这是我在两天里第一次出来呼吸到新鲜的空气
It's the first time I could come up for air in nearly two days.
我想让你知道
I wanted you to know.
你什么时候回来
When are you coming home?
跟平常一样
Usual.
- 不会很晚的
- 好吧
Not till late. Okay.
那我们到时候见
Well, I'll see you then.
跟着这些标记 然后...
Just follow the tags, and...
在里面
In there.
- 这是什么
- 我们和你的联系方式
What's this? How we'll contact you.
把它记下来 还有用来掩饰的故事
Memorize it. Also your cover story.
以及你从我这儿得到的情报
让你来这里显得更有说服力
The information you pried out of me that justifies your coming here.
这样我们才能毁了你们整个组织
It's how we took down your network.
- 这是真的情报?
- 都是可核实的
Is it true? It's verifiable.
情报的来源是谁
Who is the source?
如果我要去伊朗 我就得把内奸揪出来
If I go to Iran, I'll have to take the traitor out.
- 你知道的
- 源头就是我们的一次黑客入侵
You know that. The source is a hack we did,
一种可以让我们监听你们通讯的电脑病毒
a computer virus that allowed us to monitor your communications.
如果你想带走它 就带走吧 我们有你就够了
You want to take it out, go ahead. We have you now.
是时候回到你的人民身边了 准备好没
It's time to go back to your people. You ready?
好了
Yeah.
你打算怎么做 把我完全排除在情况之外吗
What were you planning to do, bypass me entirely?
我不会道歉的 这事只能有小部分人知道
I'm not going to apologize. I had to keep the circle small.
范围也太小了 你 Carrie Quinn
Not that small. You, Carrie, Quinn.
现在想想看 我也很久没看见那个头巾女了
And come to think of it, I haven't seen that headscarf for a while.
- 知道这些就够了
- 我还以为我们彼此信任
All need-to-know. I thought we trusted each other.
就你一个
Just you.
- 我只能再让你一个人知道
- 我不认为这可行
I tell just you. I don't see how.
Lockhart正在你的办公室等着你
You've got Lockhart waiting in your office.
你觉得他不会发现伊斯兰革命卫队头目的前妻
在Bethesda被杀了吗
You think he didn't notice that the ex-wife of the IRGC Chief got slaughtered in Bethesda?
或者是被你送进精神病院的Carrie
Or that Carrie, whom you committed to a psych ward,
已经出来了而你也不管吗
got out and you're doing shit about it?
他是参议院情报委员会的老大
不是让你逗着玩的猴子
He's the head of the Senate Intelligence Committee, not some civilian fuck-monkey.
知道了
Okay.
我是在暗中操作一些事 一项行动
I do have something going. An operation...
得了吧 直接告诉我细节
And we're past that. It's time for details.
好吧
Fine.
我直接一起告诉你们两个人
I'll tell you both.
你从没告诉我那是谁的主意
You never told me whose idea it was.
把你当鱼饵丢出去
To hang you out as bait.
是你的主意还是Saul的?
Was it your idea or Saul's?
好吧
That's all right.
你不说我也知道 那是Saul的主意
You don't have to say. It was Saul's idea.
肯定是 事实上这是Saul的典型做法
It had to be. In fact, it's classic Saul.
- 如果是典型的 那你怎么上钩了
- 你觉得呢
If it's so classic, why'd you fall for it? Why do you think?
是因为你
It was you.
你所承受的虐待
The abuse you went through.
Saul为了引我过来而对你做的一切
What Saul did to you to get me here.
连我都没有干过这么残忍的事
Even I have never done anything so cruel.
你总是忘了 我见过你的杰作的
You're forgetting I've seen your handiwork.
- 你没办法糊弄我
- 我没有糊弄你
You can't bullshit me. I'm not bullshitting you.
那么你一定是在臆想了
Then you're seriously deluded.
- 你知道他问了我什么吗
- 你为什么杀了你妻子吗
You know what he asked me? Why you killed your wife?
谁动了那颗炸弹 如果真的是Brody
Who moved the bomb. If it was Brody.
他为什么会这么问我
Now, why would he ask me that?
这说明关于那件事情是有分歧的
That implies that there's a difference of opinion on that subject.
是吧?
Right?
你怎么回答他的
What'd you tell him?
告诉他是Abu Nazir的人干的
That it was one of Abu Nazir's guys.
不是Brody?
Not Brody?
不是
No.
谁
Who?
其他人
Someone else.
我仅仅知道这些了
That's all I know.
你是Peter Quinn?
You Peter Quinn?
呃...是的
Uh, yeah.
怎么了 这个问题很难回答吗
What? That's a difficult question?
- 没有
- 因为你的同伴Mathison一直坚持你叫Candor
No. 'Cause your compadre Mathison, she promised what she called "Candor. "
Peter Quinn是...
Peter Quinn is, uh...
- 什么
- 我的真名
What? My legal name.
受害人中的一个是伊朗人
Uh, one of the victims, she was Iranian.
是的
Yes.
是一名伊斯兰革命卫队成员的前妻吗
Ex-wife of an Iranian security guy... IRGC?
- 是的
- 而另一个受害人是她的儿媳?
Yes. And the other victim, that's his daughter-in-law?
- 是的
- 我想这件事一定很重要
Yes. I assume that's significant.
是的
Right.
你的回答够简洁的
These are some terse responses.
- 我们能直接走程序了吗
- 走程序?
Look, can we just get on with this? "On with this"?
我们就是在走程序 我们怎么不是在走程序
We are "On with it. " How are we not "On with it"?
- 我的同事说你们接受认罪了
- 并不是这样
My colleague led me to believe you were after a confession. Well, that's incorrect.
我刚才说这些是为了搞清楚这儿发生了什么
What I said was, I'm trying to understand what happened here.
- 那是不可能的
- 她也是这么说的
That's not gonna be possible. Yeah, that's what she said.
她说我只需要知道这件事关系到国家安全
She said all I need to know is that it's national security.
就这些 就这些
This is. This.
听着 你或许觉得我就是个混球
能在这儿教训你
Look, I know you think I'm just some dick jacking you up because I can,
只是因为你运气不好被拍到了
'cause you were unlucky enough to get yourself photographed.
也许就是这样 我也不知道
但事实上...
And maybe that's true, I don't know. But actually,
我只是在尽量搞清楚你们这些人所干的好事
I'm just trying to understand this shit that you people do.
这堆我们得齐心协力搞定的麻烦事
因为我们缴税了
This shit that we're a party to 'cause we pay taxes.
这些...
This...
他妈的这堆烂摊子
This shit.
所以 是你杀了她的儿媳?
So you killed the daughter?
- 是的
- 用什么杀的
Yes. With?
瓦尔特P22
A Walther P22.
她呢? 同一件武器吗
What about the mother? Same weapon?
不
No.
用的玻璃瓶
That was with a bottle.
青梅酒瓶
Plum wine.
为了国家安全
For national security.
你们这些混蛋
You fucking people.
你有没有做过什么把情况变得更糟的事
Have you ever done anything... but make things worse?
这是个很特殊的消息
This is special access information.
好的
Fine.
- 不能告诉任何人
- 明白
It can't leave this room. Understood.
说吧
So?
我招募了一名伊朗的高级官员
I've recruited a high-level Iranian asset.
伊斯兰革命卫队的副职 Majid Javadi
IRGC Deputy Chief Majid Javadi.
Javadi?
是的
Yes.
- 那个资助炸掉CIA的炸弹的人
- 没错
The man who financed the bombing of the CIA.
That's right.
你为什么要去相信他
Why on Earth would you trust him?
我们得到了一些可以让他危及他的政府的情报
We've developed information that would compromise him with his own government;
- 一堆关于他腐败的情报
- 在伊朗 腐败是无比正常的事
evidence of wholesale corruption. Which, in Iran, just means it's Tuesday.
通常我是同意的
Normally I'd agree.
但是这几千万美金原本是伊斯兰革命卫队用来
But this is tens of millions of dollars siphoned
策划恐怖袭击的秘密资金
from a secret IRGC fund designated for terrorist activities.
- 没人会觉得这是平常事的
- 所以你要挟了他
No one would look the other way. So you blackmailed him.
是的
That's right.
- 那你为什么没有告诉委员会
- 我在等时机成熟
Is there some reason you didn't tell my Committee? I was waiting for it to be real.
时机不成熟是因为正是这些情报人员
It wasn't because this is just the kind of human intelligence nonsense
导致了四个月前在这栋楼里发生的灾难?
that led to disaster right here in this building not four months ago?
相信我们的宿敌会神奇地让我们转变立场
Believing our sworn enemies will magically switch sides.
我们讨论过这事
We talked about this,
放弃你所谓的冷战什么的必要性
the need to wean you of your cold war bullshit.
- 我们同意这个问题持保留意见的
- 我不这么觉得
We agreed to disagree. I don't see it that way,
特别是十天后是我来收拾你的烂摊子
not when I'm inheriting your mess in ten days.
烂摊子
A mess.
这就是你对安插一个高级资产到
That's what you call placing a major asset inside a government
已经暗箱操作30年的政府的评价?
that's been a black box for 30 years?
你问我一直在做些什么
You asked me what I've been doing.
我告诉你了
I told you.
可以结束了吗
Are we done?
不会很久了
Not by a long shot.
我要知道详细的过程
I want to know how this happened.
快到了
Almost there.
快到了 你却还没有问
Almost there and you still haven't asked.
- 问什么
- 谁动的那个炸弹
What? Who moved the bomb.
你告诉Saul了 是Abu Nazir的人
You told Saul it was one of Abu Nazir's guys.
- 我是这么说的
- 我也已经知道了
Yes, I did. Which I already knew.
但是是谁给他钥匙的?
And who handed him the keys?
别告诉我你从来没想过这事
Don't tell me you never wondered.
我打赌你一直在想这个问题
I bet you wonder all the time.
Brody从炸弹中逃生了
Brody escaped the blast.
他知道会有爆炸吗
Did he know it was coming?
或许我已经知道这个问题的答案了
Maybe I already know the answer to that.
也许你并不知道
Maybe you don't.
好吧 我想你是不想知道真相
Fine. I guess you don't want the truth.
我想 只是我不想从你这儿知道
I do. I just don't think I'd get it from you.
好吧
Okay.
- 我想知道关于他的妻子的事
- 她怎么了
I want to know about the wife. What about her?
你招募了Javadi
然后他的老婆和儿媳妇就突然死了
You recruit Javadi, his wife's suddenly dead along with the daughter-in-law.
- 别告诉我那是巧合
- 那不是
Don't tell me that's a coincidence. It's not.
那么是谁干的
So who did it?
每次你在回答问题时的长时间沉默
You know, every time you answer a question with a big, gaping nothing,
都会让我想起我们之间是怎么一个问题
it reminds me what a problem we have, you and I.
Javadi干的
It was Javadi.
等等 你是说他就在国内?
Wait a second. You're saying he was in this country?
- 是的
- 而你知道他在
That's right. And you knew this?
我们引诱他来的 Carrie引诱他来的
We lured him here.
Carrie did.
等等
So, wait.
你们俩...
You two...
你俩在合作
You were working together.
即使你在委员会面前谴责她
Even when you were denouncing her in front of my Committee.
都是在演戏
All for show.
你知道吗
Did you know?
- 我现在才知道
- 那还有谁知道
I'm learning it now with you. Well, who did know?
该知道这事的人
Everyone who needed to.
不 是不应该知道这事的人
因为现在就有两个本不应该知道这事的人
No, everyone who needed to didn't know, because two of those people are in this room right now
对你很恼火 让Carrie过来 现在
holding their dicks. I want Carrie brought in... now.
- 她没法过来
- 为什么
She can't come here now. And why is that?
- 她很忙 她忙着把Javadi送上回伊朗的飞机
- 他还在这儿?
She's busy. She's putting Javadi on a plane back to Iran. He's still here?
禁飞那架飞机
Ground the fucking plane.
- 不行
- 禁飞那架飞机
- No. - Ground it.
我还要继续担任代理局长两个星期 你做不了主
I'm Acting Director for another two weeks. It's not your call.
- 我会告诉总统的 我发誓
- 然后呢
I'll bump this up to the President, I swear to God. Then what?
我们把Javadi曝个精光
We fry Javadi's ass publicly.
- 这是目光短浅的行为
- 这是为了正义
Well, that's shortsighted. It's justice.
这没有用 因为在德黑兰
It's ineffective... 'cause back in Tehran,
会有和他一样的人来代替他
一个我们不能控制的人
he's replaced by someone just like him who we can't control.
上次在这儿发生的袭击会一次又一次地重演
And the attack that happened here happens again and again and again.
这是一个一劳永逸的行动 它会改变一切
This is a once-in-a-lifetime operation that can transform everything.
- 整个中东
- 你听起来很兴奋啊
The entire Middle East. You sound like you're fucking high.
我会给总统打电话的
I'm calling the President.
你听见我说了什么了吗
Did you hear what I said?
我会打给他的 把电话给我
I'm calling him. Get me a goddamn phone.
好吧
Fine.
这儿
Here.
- 毁掉我们所做的一切努力
- 我甚至不愿意去回应那件事
Destroy everything we've been working for. I'm not even going to dignify that with a response.
- 你是真的什么都不明白 是吧
- 你知道吗
- You really don't get it, do you? - You know what?
我第一次觉得我明白了
For the first time, I think I really do.
我明白为什么数十年来这儿工作
都像在搞小丑表演 这个怎么用?
I see now why this place has been a fucking clown act for decades. How does this work?
我不知道
I'm not sure.
不用担心 我会搞定总统的
And don't worry. I'll handle the President.
开门
Open the door.
- 不行
- 快他妈的开门
No.
Open the goddamned door.
命令我啊
Make me.
Dar 快开门
Dar, let me out of here.
Dar?
Dar
Dar.
你们死定了 你们两个...
You're dead. Both of you son...
这他妈的干嘛
What the fuck?
你有过机会的
Well, you had your chance.
等等
Wait!
没事的
It's okay.
- 你说过你会告诉我真相
- 你也说过我不会告诉你的
You said you'd tell me the truth. And you told me I was incapable.
你或许是对的
You might be right.
但是如果你想和你相信的人聊聊的话
But if you want to talk to someone you can trust...
那个人在那里 你应该知道那个人
who was there, you should know that the man
那个制造了炸弹而且移动了SUV的人
who built the bomb and moved the SUV...
并没有像他们所说的死于爆炸
he didn't die in the explosion like they say.
据我所知 他还在国内
As far as I know, he's still in this country.
- 在哪儿
- 我不知道
Where? I don't know.
- 谁知道
- 一个你见过的人
Who does? Someone you've already met.
是他让我们聚在了一起
The man that brought us together.
你的律师? Bennett?
Your lawyer? Bennett?
不 相信我 事情搞成这样了
No. The way this worked out, believe me,
他不会再是我的律师了
he's not my lawyer anymore.
是您下令让雷达360度扫描的吗
You requested radar following on Three Six Oscar?
是的
Yes.
雷达已经于22点19分扫描完了美国领空
That aircraft cleared US airspace at 2219 hours.
- 谢谢
- 好的 长官
Thank you. Yes, sir.
大胆的行动
An audacious operation.
才刚刚开始
Just the beginning.
为接下来的成功干杯
Here's to continued success.
你得知道
You know, I do need to apologize...
我应当为把事情瞒着你而道歉
for excluding you.
你不需要为自己解释 Saul
You don't have to explain yourself, Saul.
你是中央情报局的代理局长
You are the goddamn Acting Director of the Central Intelligence Agency.
还得再当10天呢
For ten more days.
Lockhart参议员不小心把他自己锁在会议室里了
Senator Lockhart managed to get himself stuck in the conference room.
你能让管理处把他弄出来吗
Could you ask facilities to let him out?
- 情况如何了
- 他们让步了
How'd it go? They're standing down.
还挺顺利
So it went well.
他们说什么来着 坦白对于灵魂有好处
What do they say, confession is good for the soul?
只是你根本没做错什么
Only you didn't do it.
我知道
I know.
但我的确感觉好了些
But it made me feel better.
我想 是正确的人 错误的罪行吧
Wrong crime, right guy, I guess.
你知道我还想清楚什么了吗
You know what else I realized?
我和CIA之间的关系
Just how through I am with...
彻彻底底地...
this, the CIA.
我什么也不会相信了
I just do not believe anymore.
相信什么
Believe what?
那些使我们造成的伤害变得理所应当的借口
That anything justifies the damage we do.
你还不能退出
You can't quit yet.
Javadi正飞越大西洋回家
Javadi's out over the Atlantic heading home.
在他离开之前...他告诉我了一些事
关于兰利的炸弹的事
And he told me something before he left... about the Langley bomber.
- 你是说Brody
- 不是他 这才是问题
You mean Brody. No, that's just it.
不是他干的 而我现在就能证明
It's not him, and I can prove it now.
但是...
But...
我需要你的帮助
I need your help.
Quinn?
当然了 Carrie
Sure, Carrie.
我会尽全力的
Whatever you need.
Saul...
今天过得怎样
How-how was your day?
挺好的
Had a good day.
实际上 过得非常好
Actually a really good day.
原谅我
Forgive me.
原谅你什么
For what?
我几乎忘了
I'd forgotten...
你有多么漂亮了
how beautiful you are.
破烂熊字幕组
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
欢迎加入
破烂熊字幕组
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
欢迎加入